Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Artists Files
  - Greengold, Jane, 2001, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Greengold, Jane, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Greengold, Jane - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Greenwood, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Grinnell, Toland, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Grooms, Red [1 of 5], undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Grooms, Red [2 of 5], undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Grooms, Red [3 of 5] (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Grooms, Red [4 of 5], undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Grooms, Red [5 of 5], undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Grooms, Red, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Gummer, Don, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Gummer, Don, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gunderson, Karen, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Gupta, Subodh, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Guston, Philip, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Haas, Richard - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Haas, Richard, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Habenicht, Wenda - Photos/Slides, 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Hadid, Zaha, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Hague, Raoul, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Halley, Peter, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Halley, Peter, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Halley, Peter, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hamilton, Ann, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Hamilton, Ann, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Hamilton-Finlay, Ian, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Hamilton-Finlay, Ian, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Hammond, Jane, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Hammons, David, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Hamrol, Lloyd, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Hamrol, Lloyd - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Hanks, David, undated (Box 13, Folder 27a)
  - Hansen, Al, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hansen, Gaylen - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Hapaska, Siobhan, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Haring, Kieth, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Haring, Kieth, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Harrison, Helen Mayer & Newton, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Harrison, Newton & Helen, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Harvey, Ellen, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Hassinger, Maren [1 of 3], undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Hassinger, Maren [2 of 3], undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Hassinger, Maren - Visuals [3 of 3], undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Hatoum, Mona, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Hawkinson, Tim, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Hayes, Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Heap of Birds, Edgar, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Heap of Birds, Edgar - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Heikoop, Govert, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Heinrich, Adrienne, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Heinrich, Adrienne, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Heinrich, Adrienne, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Heizer, Michael - Photos/Slides, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Heizer, Michael, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Held, Al [1 of 4], undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Held, Al [2 of 4], undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Held, Al [3 of 4], undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Held, Al - CDs [4 of 4], undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Held, Mara, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Helpern, Barbara - Photos/Slides, 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Henselman, Casper, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hepburn, Tony, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hepper, Carol - Photos/Slides, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Hepper, Carol, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hepper, Carol, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Herman, Nancy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Herman, Nancy - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Herring, Oliver, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Hesse, Eva, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Hickman, Robert, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Hickman, Robert, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Hicks, Sheila - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Hicks, Sheila, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Hicks, Sheila, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Highstein, Jene [1 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Highstein, Jene [2 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Highstein, Jene [3 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Highstein, Jene - "Correspondence" [4 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Highstein, Jene - "Visuals" [5 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Highstein, Jene [6 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Highstein, Jene [7 of 7], undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Highstein, Jene - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Highstein, Jene - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Hill, Gary, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Hill, Robin, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Hilliard, John, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Hinman, Charles - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Hinman, Charles - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Hockness, Celia - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Hockney, David - Photos/Slides, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Hockney, David, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Holden, Barry - Photos/Slides, 1975-1981 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Hollis, Doug, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Hollis, Doug - Photos/Slides, 1974-1985 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Hollis, Doug, undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Hollis, Doug, undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Hollis, Doug - "Criticism", undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Holt, Nancy, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Holt, Nancy - Photo, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Holt, Nancy, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Holt, Nancy - Slides, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Holup, Wopo - Slides, 1983-1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Holup, Wopo, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Holzer, Jenny - Slides, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Holzer, Jenny, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Holzer, Jenny, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Hom, Mei-Ling, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Honeycutt, Brece, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Hormeit, Martin, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Horn, Rebecca, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Horn, Roni, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Horn, Roni, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Housiary, Shirazeh, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Houston, Bruce and Housiary, Shirazeh - Slides, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Howard, Linda, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Hsu, Ti Shan - Slides, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Huang, Alan, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Hudson, Robert - Slides, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Hunt, Bryan, 1978-1994 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hunt, Bryan, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Huntington, Jim - Slides, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Hurlbut, Spring - Slides, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Huyghe, Pierre, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Hyde, James - Slides, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Iglesias, Cristina, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Indiana, Robert, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Indiana, Robert, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Insley, Will - Slides, 1964-1989 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Insley, Will, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Interactive Media Productions - "Tiffany Screensaver", undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Interactive Media Productions - "Internet", 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Interactive Media Productions - "Bicycle Screen Saver", 1996 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Interactive Media Productions CD - "Art Screensaver Correspondence", 1996 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Interactive Media Productions - "Color Xeroxer", 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Interactive Media Production/Daytona Museum, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Ireland, David, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Ireland, Patrick - Slides, 1978-1986 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Irwin, Robert - Slides, 1979-1985 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Irwin, Robert, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Isherwood, Jon, undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - J (General), undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Jaar, Alfredo, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Jackson, Oliver, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Jackson, Oliver, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Jacquette, Yvonne, undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Jacquette, Yvonne - Slides, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Jaime-Mena, Susana - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Jaime-Mena, Susana - Photos/Slides, 1987-1993 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Janney, Christopher, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Janney, Christopher, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Jaudon, Valerie - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jaudon, Valerie, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jetlova - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Jimenez, Luis - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Johanson, P., undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Jonas, Joan, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Jones/Ginzel, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Jones/Ginzel [1 of 6], undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Jones/Ginzel - "Bios" [2 of 6], undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Jones/Ginzel - Correspondence [3 of 6], undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Jones/Ginzel - "Critical Material" [4 of 6], undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Jones/Ginzel [5 of 6], undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Jones/Ginzel [6 of 6], undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Jones, Kristin, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Ronald, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Juarez, Roberto, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Judd, Donald [1 of 2], undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Judd, Donald [2 of 2], undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Judd, Donald - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - K (General), undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - KCHO, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Kabakov, Ilya, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Kaiser, Eshkar & Paul, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Kane, Bill - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Kane, Bill - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Kane, Bill - Reviews, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Kaneko, Jun, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Kang, Ik-Joong, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Kapoor, Anish - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Kapoor, Anish, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Kaprov, S., undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Kaprov, Susan, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Kaprow, Allan, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Karavan, Dani, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Karpeles, Eric, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Kasten, Barbara, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Katz, Alex, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Katz, Joel, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Kaufman, Jane, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Kaufman, Jane, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Kaufman, Jane, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Kaufman, Jane - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Kawai, Misaki, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Keech, Pamela, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Keister, Steve [1 of 2], undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Keister, Steve [2 of 2], undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Keister, Steve - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Kelley, Mike, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Kelley, Mike, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Kendrick, Mel - Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Kendrick, Mel, 1991, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Kentridge, William, 2000, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kessler, Jon, 1988-1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kessler, Jon - Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kleinberg, Susan, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Khedoori, Toba, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kilmnik, Karen, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kimsooja, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - King, Mary, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - King, Mary, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kinnebrew, Joseph, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kirili, Alain, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kirili, Alain, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Kirkland, Linda - Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Kisch, Gloria - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Kisch, Gloria - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Klagsbrun, Nicole - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Knowlton, Win - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Knowlton, Win - Photos/Slides, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Knowlton, Win - Reviews, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Knowlton, Win - Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Koenigsberg, Nancy, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Koester, Joachim - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Koons, Jeff - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Koons, Jeff - Reviews, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Koons, Jeff - Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Kos, Paul - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Kotik, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Kounellis, J. - Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Kozloff - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Kozloff - Critical, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Kozloff - Visuals, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Kozloff, Joyce - SF Airport, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Kozloff, Joyce [1 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Kozloff, Joyce [2 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Kruger, Barbara - Photos/Slides, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Kruger, Barbara - Reviews, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Kruger, Barbara - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Krushenic, Nicholas - Photos/Slides, 1968-1981 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Kulicke, Barbara - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Kulicke, Barbara - Photos/Slides, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Kulicke, Barbara - Reviews, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Kulicke, Barbara - Proposals, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Kunce, Samm - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Kunce, Samm - Photos/Slides, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Kunce, Samm - Reviews, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Kusama, Yayo - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Kusama, Yayo - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Kushner, Robert [1 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Kushner, Robert [2 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Kushner, Robert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Kushner, Robert - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Kushner, Robert - Reviews, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Kulansky, Eli - Photos/Slides, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - LaFontain, Marie - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - LaFontain, Marie - Reviews, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - LaFontain, Marie - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - La Lanne, Claude & Francois-Xavier, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Labriola, Liz, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Lachowicz, Rachel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1992-1999 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Lachowicz, Rachel - Photos/Slides, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Lachowicz, Rachel - Reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ladda, Justen - Photos/Slides, 1981-1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Ladda, Justen - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Ladda, Justen, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Lambri, Luisa - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Lang, Gary - Photos/Slides, 1990-1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Lang, Gary - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Lang, Gary - Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Langager, Craig - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lanyon, Ellen - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Lanyon, Ellen - Photos/Slides, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Laramee, Eve Andree, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Larner, Liz, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Larner, Liz - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Larner, Liz - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Larner, Liz - Reviews, 1991-1999 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Larsen, Mernet - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Larsen, Mernet - Photos/Slides, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Latham, John, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - LaVerdiere, Julian - Reviews, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Lawson, Thomas - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Lawson, Thomas - Reviews, 1985-1997 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Lawson, Thomas, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Lazzarini, Robert, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - LaDray, Charles - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - LaDray, Charles - Photos/Slides, 1991-1996 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - LaDray, Charles - Reviews, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Lee, Billy, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Lee, Catherine - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Lee, Jenny, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Leedy, Jim - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - LeFevre, Gregg - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - LeFevre, Gregg - Photos/Slides, 1986-1994 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - LeFevre, Gregg - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Legar, Fernand - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Legar, Fernand - Reviews, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Legar, Fernand - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Leger, Ferdinand - NYC Project, undated (Box 18, Folder 48a)
  - Leicester, Andrew, 1978-1989 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Leicester, Andrew, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Leirner, Jac - Photos/Slides, 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Leirner, Jac - Reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Leirner, Jac - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Lemieux, Annette - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Lemieux, Annette - Photos/Slides, 1986-2000 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Leopold, Susan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1993-2000 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Leopold, Susan - Photos/Slides, 1992-1999 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Leopold, Susan - Reviews, 1990-1998 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Lerman, Ora, 1988-1995 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Le Va, Barry, undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Le Va, Barry - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Le Va, Barry - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Le Va, Barry - Reviews, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Levine, Erik, undated (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Levine, Erik - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Levine, Les - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1990-1997 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Levy, Stacy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Levy, Stacy - Photos/Slides, 1991-1996 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Lewis, Ross, undated (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - LeWitt, Sol - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - LeWitt, Sol - Photos/Slides, 1980-1995 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - LeWitt, Sol - Reviews, undated (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - LeWitt, Sol, undated (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - LeWitt, Sol, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Liberman, Alexander, undated (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Liberman, Alexander, undated (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Lichtenstein, Miranda, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, undated (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, undated (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Liddell, Siobhan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Lin, Maya, undated (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Lindfors, Stefan, undated (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Lipski, Donald - Reviews, 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Lipski, Donald, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Lobe, Robert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997-2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Lobe, Robert - Photos/Slides, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lobe, Robert - Reviews, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lobe, Robert, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lomahaftewa, Dan, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Long, Richard, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Long, Richard, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Long, Richard - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Longo, Richard, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Loring, John, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - LOT/EK Archive - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - LOT/EK Archive - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Lou, Liza - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Lou, Liza - Reviews, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Lou, Liza - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Louden, Sharon - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Louden, Sharon, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Louden, Sharon - Photos/Slides, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Louden, Sharon - Reviews, 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Louie, Jeannette - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Louie, Jeannette - Photos/Slides, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Louie, Jeannette - Reviews, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Love, Arlene, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Loving, Al, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Lucier, Mary, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Lucier, Mary - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1984-1996 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Lucier, Mary - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Lucier, Mary - Reviews, 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Lucier, Mary - Proposals, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Luckey, Thomas, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Lukas, Emil - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Lukas, Emil - Photos/Slides, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Lukas, Emil, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Lutter, Vera - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Lutz, Winifred [1 of 5], undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Lutz, Winifred [2 of 5], undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Lutz, Winifred [3 of 5], undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Lutz, Winifred (Photos) [4 of 5], undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Lutz, Winifred [5 of 5], undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Lutz, Winifred, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Luyten, Mark, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Lynde, Clyde, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Lyons, Ruth Ava, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Lyten, Mark - Reviews, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Lyten, Mark - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - MacDonald, Elizabeth - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
    General
    Contains broken tile sample
  - MacDonald, Elizabeth, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - MacDonald, Elizabeth - Reviews, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - MacDonald, Elizabeth - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Mach, David - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994-2006 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Mach, David - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Mach, David - Reviews, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Madigan, Martha - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Madigan, Martha - Photos/Slides, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Madigan, Martha - Reviews, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Madsen, Loren [1 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Madsen, Loren [2 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Madsen, Loren [3 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Madsen, Loren [4 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Madsen, Loren, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Madsen, Loren, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Manship, Paul, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Marcaccio, Fabien, Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Marcheschi, Cork, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Marcheschi, Cork, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Marden, Brice, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Marden, Brice, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)